FEMALE TEXT-TO-SPEECH VOICE:
Top of the morning to you.
You've reached Maggie McGarry.
(Mechanical voice on Sheldon's phone:)Leave a message
after the wee little beep.
(Sheldon:)It's pretty convincing, huh?
That wasn't even
a real person.
(Sheldon:)And here is
the clincher:
(Sheldon:)a lock of Maggie's
flaming auburn hair.
Where'd you get that?
(Sheldon:)From an orangutan
in the primate lab.
(Leonard:)An orangutan?
Well, no one's going
(Sheldon:)to run a DNA test
on it, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Honestly, you overthink
everything.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I don't need an alibi.
(Leonard:)Nobody's going to ask
about last night
(Leonard:)as long as you just
zip your lip.
Thank you.
(Leonard:)Now, don't worry,
everything is going to be fine.